<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dominika Woszczyk</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dominika Woszczyk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/</guid>
      <description>\cvsection{Talks}
\cvevent{\textbf{Invited Speaker @ Clarity Workshop 23&amp;rsquo;}}{Interspeech 2023}{August 2023}{Dublin, IE} Gave a talk about the Lombard effect and how it could be applied to Text-to-Speech to improve speech intelligibility and help people with hearing impairment. \vspace{1em}
\cvevent{\textbf{Impostor Syndrome Workshop}}{Bearing Point}{July 2023}{London, UK} Gave an hour-long workshop on Impostor syndrome and coping strategies to consultants from BearingPoint as part of their new DIVE (Diversity, Inclusion, Variety, and Equality) initiative. \vspace{1em}
\cvevent{\textbf{9th Doctoral Consortium}}{Interspeech 2023}{August 2023}{Dublin, IE} My abstract was selected to present my PhD thesis and progress to a panel of PhD students and experts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurial AI student stars in Bright SCIdea Challenge with mental health chatbot</title>
      <link>/entrepreneurship/brightsci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/entrepreneurship/brightsci/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marshmallow AI learning tool tops Future Worlds Startup Pitch Off</title>
      <link>/entrepreneurship/marshmallow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/entrepreneurship/marshmallow/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the startups pitching at Future Worlds Dragons’ Den</title>
      <link>/entrepreneurship/dragons_den/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/entrepreneurship/dragons_den/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lombard effect and how we could use it to help with hearing impairment</title>
      <link>/blog/23_08_26_lombard_vc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/23_08_26_lombard_vc/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered why we tend to speak louder in a noisy room? Well, speech and linguistic researchers have been curious too, and they&amp;rsquo;ve explored a concept called the Lombard Effect (discovered by Étienne Lombard).
🔊 The Lombard Effect in a Nutshell Picture yourself at a party, where the music is playing and everyone is chatting and laughing. Having a good time! To make yourself heard by your friend, your brain automatically level up your voice&amp;rsquo;s volume, tweaks your pitch and even adjust your speech speed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
